http://www.simplybeach.com/pages/privacy-information

Privacy & Cookies
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.simplybeach.com (the “Site”).
Personal Information We Collect
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
As you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site to better improve your experience. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (however, we do not hold your credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
If you agree to join our mail-list, either via our site popup, site footer email signup form, or by agreeing to receive email marketing from us on the checkout (all optional) we will store certain information such as name and email address. We refer to this information as "Marketing information"
As you progress through our checkout there is a marketing option that is optional that allows us to text you under certain scenarios too. This is optional and you can opt out of all future texts by replying with STOP to our messages. Our messages are delivered at no charge to you.
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information, Order Information & Marketing Information.
How do we use your personal information?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfil any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).
Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Request product reviews via our third party review system Okendo;
Communicate with you regarding your loyalty points (where applicable) via our third party loyalty points system Loyalty Lion;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud and under some circumstances process age verification checks (for dangerous goods etc); and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. Depending on whether you join our mail list without placing an order we also use our Marketing information for this purpose.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
Sharing Your Personal Information
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy.
We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Behavioural Advertising
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
Facebook - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
Google - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
Bing - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Do Not Track
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Your Rights
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States as that is where our website platform Shopify is based.
Data Retention
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Contact Us
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at hello@simplybeach.com.
Sign Up for our newsletter to be the first to hear about new collections and special offers
Thanks for subscribing
Sorry, this email is either incorrect or already exists on our system
icon/Facebook
Created with Sketch.
Facebook
icon/Twitter
Created with Sketch.
Twitter
Instagram
YouTube
Simply Beach uses cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue we assume that you consent to receive all cookies on Simply Beach.
Read More
Top
